http://www.logitech.com/en-us/footer/privacy

LOGITECH WEBSITE PRIVACY STATEMENT
Logitech, Inc. and its affiliates (collectively “Logitech”, “We” and “Us”) respect your privacy. This Privacy Statement explains how Logitech collects and uses personal data from visitors to its web and mobile sites that link directly to this Privacy Statement (collectively “Sites”).
Actively Submitted Data
If you call us, send us an email, or fill out a form on one of our Sites, we use the information you provide to respond to your request or to otherwise communicate with you or assist you. If you make purchases through our Sites, we may collect data necessary to process your order, such as your shipping address, products ordered, and your contact information.
Passively Provided Data
When you access our Sites, depending on your opt-in choices, certain information about your computer or mobile device is shared with us, which may include the activities you perform on our Sites, the type of hardware and software you are using, (such as your operating system or browser), information stored in cookies, IP address, access times, the web pages from which you came, the regions from which you navigate the web page, and the web pages you access. We use this information to better understand the interests of the users of our Sites, to improve our Sites, services, and products.
We do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” signals in browsers as we are trying to provide a customized website experience.
Cookies
Logitech uses cookies that are essentially small data files placed on your computer, tablet, mobile phone, or other devices. Click here to learn more about cookies.
Data use and sharing
We use the data we collect to provide you with rich, interactive experiences. In particular, we may use data to:
provide the service or carry out the transactions at your request;
improve and develop our products;
personalize your experience;
process job applications you submit through our Sites;
advertise and market to you subject to applicable legal requirements, which may include sending promotional communications, targeting advertising, and presenting you with relevant offers.
Read more
We do not sell your personal data.
We may share your personal data with third parties under certain circumstances. We use affiliated and unaffiliated service providers that help us process personal data to deliver services and run our business subject to strict confidentiality agreements. For example, service providers help deliver the following functions:
Service Description
Data Provided
Purpose
Customer Support
Contact data, Inquiry data
To help troubleshoot and support products and services
E-Commerce Functionality
Contact data, Interactions with website
To facilitate sales of our products online
Promotions and Relevant News
Contact data, Cookie data
To provide information and incentives for our products and services
Website performance
Cookie data, Interactions with website
To enable functionality and features while on our websites
Cookie Opt-In Manager
Cookie data
To provide the ability to choose cookies to be allowed on our websites
These companies are required to abide by our data protection and security requirements and are not allowed to use personal data they receive from us for any other purpose.
We may disclose your personal information to
comply with relevant laws, regulatory requirements, and to respond to lawful requests, court orders, and legal process;
to protect and defend the rights or property of us or third parties, including enforcing agreements, policies, and terms of use;
in an emergency, including to protect the safety of our employees or any person; or
in connection with investigating or preventing fraud.
We may share your personal data for purposes of a business deal, or negotiation of a business deal, involving sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets. These deals can include any merger, financing, acquisition, divestiture, joint venture or partnership, or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding.
We also freely use and share aggregated and pseudonymous information for performance and analytics purposes that cannot be used to identify you individually.
Children
We do not knowingly collect or maintain information about persons under 13 years of age. If we learn that information about persons under 13 years of age has been collected on or through the Sites, we will take appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 years of age who has registered for an account or service on our Sites, please contact us using the contact information below to have that child’s account or service terminated and personal information deleted.
Data Retention
We retain personal data for as long as necessary to provide functionality and fulfill the transactions you have requested, or for other legitimate purposes such as complying with our legal obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our agreements. Because these needs can vary for different data types, the context of our interactions with you or your use of our Sites, actual retention periods can vary significantly.
Data Security
We use TLS certificates, encryption, data access limitations, anti-virus software, and firewalls to reduce the risk of unauthorized access to personal data. No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network is entirely secure. Be mindful of security risks when you transmit personal data to us and when you post information in our public forums.
If you would like to report any security issues in any of our products, please fill out the form and required attachments and send it to Logitech Security.
EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield
Logitech, Inc. and our U.S.-based entities including Logitech Latin America Inc., participate in and have certified their compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/
Read more
We are responsible for the processing of personal data we receive, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequent transfers to third parties acting as agents on our behalf. We comply with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.
With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Logitech is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, we commit to resolving complaints about our collection or use of your personal information.
EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact us using the contact information below.
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) using the following form: https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.
For Human Resources Data Only:
We commit to cooperating with the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC), as applicable, and to comply with the advice given by such authorities, with regard to human resources data transferred from the EU and Switzerland to the United States in the context of an employment relationship.
Logitech is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (“FTC”).
Controlling and accessing your information
You may request that we update or delete/deactivate certain information pertaining to you.
If we cannot remove some personal information, we will let you know why. If you have subscribed to marketing emails, you may stop the delivery by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the email received or at the subscription management page on our Site: https://www.logitech.com/subscribe.
You also have the right to request how your data is processed and with whom we share it.
Additionally, if you believe certain information Logitech processes about you is inaccurate, you have the right to have this information corrected.
We will endeavor to respond to your request to review the information we have on file for you within 30 days from receiving such request.
If you have questions, comments, or would like to make a request regarding your data or our Statement, past Statements, and data practices, please contact us at support.logitech.com/response-center or through the following methods:
Phone: +1 646-454-3200
Email: support.logitech.com/response-center
Postal Mail: Logitech Privacy Officer, 7700 Gateway Blvd., Newark, CA 94560 USA
If you are not satisfied with our response, you can refer your privacy complaint or dispute to the relevant state or national data protection authority in your jurisdiction.
Privacy Rights for California Residents
Under the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”), California residents have certain rights around Logitech's collection, use, and sharing of their personal information. Logitech does not sell your personal information and will not do so in the future without providing you with notice and an opportunity to opt-out of such sale as required by law. Similarly, we do not offer financial incentives associated with our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information.
Read more
Logitech collects various categories of personal information when you use the Service, including identifiers, commercial information, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, geolocation data, and professional information. A more detailed description of the information We collect and how we use it, the categories of third parties with whom we share personal information, and what information may be shared under different circumstances in the policy above.
If you are a resident of California, you have the right to request to know what personal information has been collected about you, and to access that information. You also have the right to request deletion of your personal information, though exceptions under the CCPA may allow Logitech to retain and use certain personal information notwithstanding your deletion request. You can learn more about how to submit a data rights request through contact details located within this policy. You may also send your request by email to privacy@logitech.com. We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights under the CCPA. An agent may submit a request on your behalf, but you must verify that your agent is authorized to do so.
Separate from the CCPA, California’s Shine the Light law gives California residents the right to ask companies what personal information they share with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. We do not disclose your personal information to third parties for the purpose of directly marketing their goods or services to you unless you request such disclosure. If you have any questions regarding this policy, or would like to change your preferences, you may contact us at the address listed in this policy.
Effective date
This Privacy Statement is effective February 24, 2020.
